("God Bless the USA"
by Lee Greenwood")
♪ If tomorrow all the
things were gone ♪
♪ I'd worked for all my life ♪
♪ And I had to start again ♪
♪ With just my
children and my wife ♪
♪ I'd thank my lucky stars ♪
♪ To be living here today ♪
♪ 'Cause the flag still
stands for freedom ♪
♪ And they can't
take that away ♪
♪ And I'm proud to
be an American ♪
♪ Where at least
I know I'm free ♪
♪ And I won't forget
the men who died ♪
♪ Who gave that right to me ♪
♪ And I'd gladly
stand up next to you ♪
♪ And defend her still today ♪
♪ 'Cause there ain't no doubt ♪
♪ I love this land ♪
♪ God Bless the USA ♪
♪♪♪
♪ From the lakes of Minnesota ♪
♪ To the hills of Tennessee ♪
♪ Across the plains of Texas ♪
♪ From sea to shining sea ♪
♪ From Detroit down to Houston ♪
♪ And New York to LA ♪
♪ Well, there's pride in
every American heart ♪
♪ And it's time
we stand and say ♪
♪ That I'm proud
to be an American ♪
♪ Where at least
I know I'm free ♪
♪ And I won't forget
the men who died ♪
♪ Who gave that right to me ♪
♪ And I'd gladly
stand up next to you ♪
♪ And defend her still today ♪
♪ 'Cause there ain't no doubt ♪
♪ I love this land ♪
♪ God Bless the USA ♪
♪ And I'm proud to
be an American ♪
♪ Where at least
I know I'm free ♪
♪ And I won't forget
the men who died ♪
♪ Who gave that right to me ♪
♪ And I'd gladly stand up ♪
♪ Next to you ♪
♪ And defend her still today ♪
♪ 'Cause there ain't no doubt ♪
♪ I love this land ♪
♪ God Bless the USA ♪